Guide to the BOMB Magazine Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: BOMB Publications, 1981-2005
  - Subseries II.1: Issues, 1981-2005
    - Issue 36, 1991 Summer
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 28, 68)
      - Issue (Box 116)
    - Issue 37, 1991 Fall
      - General (Box 109)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 109)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches, 5 ¼ inches) (Box 68, 71, 109)
      - Issue (Box 116)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 109)
    - Issue 38, 1991-1992 Winter
      - General (Box 99)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 99)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches, 5 ¼ inches) (Box 68, 99)
      - Issue (Box 116)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 99)
    - Issue 39, 1992 Spring
      - General (Box 25)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 25, 68, 71)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Photographs (Box 25)
      - Printed Material (Box 25)
    - Issue 40, 1992 Summer
      - General (Box 103)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 71)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs--Summercoming by Cory Brown (Box 103)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 103)
      - Publicity Photographs (Box 103)
    - Issue 41, 1992 Falll
      - General (Box 103)
      - Audio Files--Audio Casettes (Box 111)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68, 71)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Printed Material--Playbill--Fires in the Mirror (Box 103)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - The Living End (Box 103)
        - Smith, Anna Deveare (Box 103)
    - Issue 42, 1992-1993 Winter
      - General (Box 54)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 54)
      - Art--Slides (Box 54)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 54, 68, 71)
      - Issue (Box 3)
      - Publicity Photographs (Box 54)
    - Issue 43, 1993 Spring
      - General (Box 3)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 111)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 3)
      - Publicity Photographs (Box 3)
    - Issue 44, 1993 Summer
      - General (Box 44)
      - Art--Slides (Box 44)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (5 ¼ inches) (Box 44, 68, 71)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs--A Gathering of Crows by John Patrick Shanley, 1993 (Box 44)
    - Issue 45, 1993 Fall
      - General (Box 3)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 3, 71)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 3)
      - Publicity Photographs (Box 3)
    - Issue 46, 1993-1994 Winter
      - General (Box 14)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 14)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Journal--Performing Arts, Los Angeles Edition, Vol. 26, No. 2, 1992 February (Box 14)
      - Portrait Photographs--Graham, Dan (Box 14)
      - Printed Material--Artist's Catalog--Graham, Dan, 1993 (Box 14)
      - Publicity Photographs--The Scent of Green Papaya (Box 14)
    - Issue 47, 1994 Spring
      - General (Box 93)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 71)
      - Interview--Foreman, Richard (Box 57)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 93)
      - Publicity Photographs (Box 93)
    - Issue 48, 1994 Summer
      - General (Box 88)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 71)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 88)
        - The Elephants of Reckoning by Indran Amirthanayagam (Box 88)
        - suburbia by Eric Bogosian (Box 88)
      - Photographs--General (Box 88)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 88)
      - Publicity Photographs (Box 88)
    - Issue 49, 1994 Fall
      - General (Box 50)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 50)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 50)
    - Issue 50, 1995-1995 Winter
      - General (Box 8)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 8)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Audio Files--Micro Cassettes--Lee-Yiny Lee (Box 50)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68, 71)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Layout (Box 8)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 8)
      - Publicity Photographs (Box 8)
    - Issue 51, 1995 Spring
      - General (Box 40)
      - Art--Photographs--"Absolut Dickson" by Beth Phillips (Box 40)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Layout (Box 8)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs--Gringa Latina: A Woman of Two Worlds by Gabriella De Ferrari, 1995 (Box 40)
      - Portrait Photographs
        - Cachao (Box 40)
        - Hatfield, Juliana (Box 40)
        - Lee, Li-Young (Box 40)
        - Morrow, Brad (Box 40)
        - Unidentified Woman (Box 40)
      - Printed Material
        - Book Catalog--University Press of New England (Box 40)
        - Playbill--Hapgood at Lincoln Center (Box 40)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - Antigone at the Yale Repertory Theater (Box 40)
        - The Death of the Last Black Man in the Whole Entire World at the Yale Repertory Theater (Box 40)
        - Priest (Box 40)
        - Saint Joan of the Stockyards at the Yale Repertory Theater (Box 40)
        - School for Wives at the Yale Repertory Theater (Box 40)
        - Shallow Grave (Box 40)
    - Issue 52, 1995 Summer
      - General (Box 26)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 26)
        - Medeski, Martin & Wood (Box 26)
        - Unidentified Individuals (Box 26)
    - Issue 53, 1995 Fall
      - General (Box 72)
      - Art--Photographs--Goldberg, Jim (Box 72)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68, 71)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Layout (Box 72)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs--Zombie by Joyce Carol Oates (Box 72)
      - Portrait Photographs
        - Blue Explosion (Box 72)
        - Brock-Broido, Lucy (Box 72)
        - Cebar, Paul (Box 72)
        - Hargrove, Roy (Box 72)
        - Jordan, June (Box 72)
        - West, Dorothy (Box 72)
    - Issue 54, 1995-1996 Winter
      - General (Box 39)
      - Art--Photographs and slides--Cheang, Shu Lea (Box 39)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Proofs (Box 39)
        - "The Law of Enclosures" by Dale Peck (Box 39)
        - "Little" by David Treuer (Box 39)
      - Portrait Photographs--Peck, Dale (Box 39)
      - Publicity Photographs--Leaving Las Vegas (Box 39)
    - Issue 55, 1996 Spring
      - General (Box 21, 56)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 56)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs
        - "Fling with a Demon Lover" by Kelvin Christopher James (Box 117)
        - "Hey Joe" by Ben Neihart (Box 117)
      - Printed Material--"Look Away! Look Away! Look Away!" by Kara Elizabeth Walter (Box 56)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - Fargo (Box 56)
        - The United States of Poetry (Box 56)
        - The White Balloon (Box 56)
    - Issue 56, 1996 Summer
      - General (Box 15)
      - Art--Slides--Michener, Diana (Box 15)
      - Artist's Catalog--Buvoli, Luca, 1994 (Box 15)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 15)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs--The World of Jeffrey Vallance, edited by David A. Greene and Gary Kornblau (Box 15)
      - Portrait Photographs
        - Coleman, Ornette and Denardo (Box 15)
        - Hahn, Ulla (Box 15)
        - Welsh, Irvine (Box 15)
      - Publicity Photographs--Films Produced by Miramax (Box 15)
    - Issue 57, 1996 Fall
      - General (Box 33)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 33, 68)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs--The Apprentice by Lewis Libby (Box 33)
      - Portrait Photographs
        - Artists Profiled in Editor's Choice (Box 33)
        - Scott, Elliot (Box 33)
        - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum (Box 33)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - The Adventures of Priscilla, Queen of the Desert (Box 33)
        - The Birdcage (Box 33)
        - Secrets & Lies (Box 33)
    - Issue 58, 1996-1997 Winter
      - General (Box 22)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 22, 68, 71)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 22)
        - "Arcade: Poems" by Erica Hunt, 1996 (Box 22)
        - "Famine" by Todd Komarnicki, 1997 (Box 22)
        - "Guided Tours of Hell" by Francine Prose (Box 22)
        - "My Drowning" by Jim Grimsley (Box 22)
        - "The Ordinary Seaman," 1997 (Box 22)
        - "Stuart Hall: Critical Dialogues in Cultural Studies," 1996 (Box 22)
        - "The Women" by Hilton Als, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Portrait Photographs
        - Grimsley, Jim, undated (Box 22)
        - Hunt, Erica, 1996 April (Box 22)
        - Hunt, Erica and Saar, Alison, 1996 May (Box 22)
        - Komarnicki, Todd, 1997 (Box 22)
        - Ondaatje, Michael, 1996 November (Box 22)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - The English Patient, 1996 (Box 22)
        - Films Produced by Miramax, 1997 Winter/Spring (Box 22)
        - The People vs. Larry Flint (Box 22)
        - The Substance of Fire (Box 22)
      - Issue 59, 1997 Spring (Box 22)
      - General (Box 35)
      - Art--Photographs--Sullivan, Billy (Box 35)
      - Art--Slides
        - Kahn, Wolf (Box 35)
        - Schneemann, Carolee (Box 35)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Layout (Box 83)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 35)
        - "The Keepsake" by Kirsty Gunn (Box 35)
        - Proof of Love and Longing in Bombay: Stories by Vikram Chandra, 1997 (Box 35)
        - Van Gogh's Bad Café: A Love Story by Frederic Tuten, 1997 (Box 35)
        - Watusi Titanic: Poems by Connie Deanovich (Box 35)
        - Wild Kingdon: Poems by Vijay Seshardi, 1996 (Box 35)
      - Portrait Photographs
        - Moody, Rick (Box 35)
        - Unidentified Children and Plants (Box 35)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - Everyone Says I Love You, 1996 (Box 35)
        - Rosewood, 1997 (Box 35)
        - When the Cat's Away, undated (Box 35)
    - Issue 60, 1997 Summer
      - General (Box 83)
      - Art--Photographs
        - Dill, Lesley, 1994 (Box 83)
        - Ireland, David, undated (Box 83)
        - Le Va, Barry, 1990 (Box 83)
        - Unidentified Artist, undated (Box 83)
      - Art--Slides--Swansea, Ena (Box 83)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files (Box 68, 71, 83)
        - Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68, 71, 83)
        - Zip Disks (Box 68, 71, 83)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Layout (Box 83)
      - Portrait Photographs
        - Agha Shahid Ali (Box 83)
        - Harris, Emmylou (Box 83)
        - Mehldau, Brad (Box 83)
      - Printed Material
        - Artist's Catalog--Le Va, Barry, 1996 (Box 83)
        - Exhibition Catalog--"Paradise Alley" by Jane Dickson, 1996 (Box 83)
        - Playbill--The Last Night of Ballyhoo at the Helen Hayes Theatre, undated (Box 83)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - The Designated Mourner, undated (Box 83)
        - Gridlock'd, 1996 (Box 83)
        - The Hairy Ape--Wooster Group Theatre Production, undated (Box 83)
        - When We Were Kings, undated (Box 83)
        - Unidentified Film, undated (Box 83)
    - Issue 61, 1997 Fall
      - General (Box 4, 96)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files
        - Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 4, 9, 71, 96)
        - Zip Disks (Box 68)
      - Editorial Notes (Box 9)
      - Issue (Box 117)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs
        - "The Devil's Chimney" by Anne Landsman, 1997 (Box 96)
        - The Embroidered Shoes: Stories by Can Xue, 1997 September (Box 4)
        - "Jesus Saves" by Darcey Steinke (Box 4)
        - "The Mercy Street" by Rilla Askew (Box 96)
        - The Skull of Charlotte Corday & Other Stories by Leslie Dick, 1995 (Box 4)
      - Photographs--General (Box 96)
      - Portrait Photographs
        - Horowitz, Richard and Deyhim, Sussan, undated (Box 96)
        - Landsman, Anne, undated (Box 96)
        - Murakami, Haruki, undated (Box 96)
        - Parker, Mary-Louise and Vogel, Paula, undated (Box 4)
      - Printed Material--Playbill--How I Learned to Drive at the Vineyard Theatre, undated (Box 96)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - Different for Girls, 1996 (Box 4)
        - Fast, Cheap & Out of Control, 1997 (Box 4)
        - Habit, undated (Box 96)
        - Intimate Relations, undated (Box 4)
        - Mrs. Dalloway, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Issue 62, 1997-1998 Winter
      - General (Box 84, 90)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 84)
        - Pearson, Bruce (Box 84)
        - Prieto, Monique (Box 84)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files
        - Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 9, 68, 71, 84)
        - Zip Disks (Box 68)
      - Editorial Notes (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 84)
        - "The Fiery Pantheon" by Nancy Lehman (Box 84)
        - "A Heart so White" by Javier Marias, 1995 (Box 84)
        - "Jack Maggs" by Peter Carey, 1998 (Box 84)
      - Portrait Photograph--Amis, Martin (Box 84)
      - Printed Material
        - Artist's Catalog--Murray, Elizabeth (Box 90)
        - Playbill--A Madhouse in Goa at the Second Stage Theatre, 1997 November (Box 84)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - Bent, 1997 (film) (Box 84)
        - The Kingdom II, undated (Box 84)
        - A Madhouse in Goa, 1997 November (Box 84)
        - Welcome to Sarajevo, 1997 (Box 84)
    - Issue 63, 1998 Spring
      - General (Box 79)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files (Box 68, 79)
        - Floppy Disks, (3 ½ inches) (Box 68, 79)
        - Zip Disks (Box 68, 79)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs
        - "Quarantine" by Jim Crace, 1997 (Box 25)
        - Remote Feed: Stories by David Gilbert (Box 79)
      - Portrait Photographs
        - General (Box 79)
        - Howard, Maureen, 1998 (Box 79)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - General (Box 79)
        - Men with Guns, 1997 (Box 79)
    - Issue 64, 1998 Summer
      - General (Box 9)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 112)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 118)
    - Issue 65, 1998 Fall
      - General (Box 17)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 112)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 9, 12, 17)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 68)
      - Editorial Notes (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Portrait Photographs
        - Grimsely, Jim, undated (Box 12)
        - Ozick, Cynthia, undated (Box 17)
      - Publicity Slides--Apt Pupil (Box 17)
    - Issue 66, 1998-1999 Winter
      - General (Box 76, 91)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 91)
        - English, Simon (Box 91)
        - Kerlin, Sherry (Box 91)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 71)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 76)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 71)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Layout (Box 1)
      - Printed Material--Journal. Amnesia, Vol. 5 no. 48, 1998 (Box 91)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - Beloved, undated (Box 91)
        - The Celebration, 1998 October (Box 91)
        - Central Station, undated (Box 91)
        - Daryl Roth Theatre, undated (Box 91)
        - George Wallace, 1997 (Box 76)
    - Issue 67, 1999 Spring
      - General (Box 24, 75)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 75)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 68, 71)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Layout (Box 80, 81)
      - Portrait Photographs--Warner, Alan, 1999 (Box 75)
      - Publicity Photographs--Hallelujah! Ron Athey: A Story of Deliverance, undated (Box 75)
      - Publicity Photographs--Wanamaker, Zoe and Taylor, Myra Lucretia, undated (Box 24)
    - Issue 68, 1999 Summer
      - General (Box 51)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 51)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 51, 71)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 68, 71)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Layout (Box 80)
      - Portrait Photographs--Hahn, Kimilo, undated (Box 51)
      - Printed Material--Playbill--Ashes to Ashes, Roundabout Theatre Company, undated (Box 51)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - Ashes to Ashes, Roundabout Theatre Company, undated (Box 51)
        - Cookie's Fortune, 1999 (Box 51)
        - The Icemen Cometh, Brooks Atkinson Theatre, undated (Box 51)
    - Issue 69, 1999 Fall
      - General (Box 51)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassette
        - General (Box 113)
        - Cezair-Thompson, Margaret (Box 48)
        - Ginzberg, Carlo (Box 48)
        - Rand, Archie (Box 48)
        - Said, Edward, 1999 July 22 (Box 48)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 71)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 48, 71)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 68, 71)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Layout (Box 81)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 48)
        - Anderson, Laurie, undated (Box 48)
        - Cezair-Thompson, Margaret, undated (Box 48)
        - Estep, Maggie, undated (Box 48)
        - Gray, Macy, 1999 (Box 48)
        - Harvey, P.J., undated (Box 48)
        - Lhasa, undated (Box 48)
        - Poirier, Mark Jude, undated (Box 48)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - Acid House, 1998? (Box 48)
        - Affliction, undated (Box 48)
        - Being John Malkovich, 1999 (Box 48)
        - Cookie's Fortune, 1999 (Box 48)
        - George Wallace, 1997 (Box 48)
        - Happy, Texas, 1999 (Box 48)
    - Issue 70, 1999-2000 Winter (Americas)
      - General (Box 53)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 71)
      - Issue (Box 71)
      - Layout (Box 81)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 53)
        - Baca, Susan, 1997 (Box 53)
        - Cura, Jose, undated (Box 53)
      - Printed Material
        - Journals--Vice Versa, number 58, 1998 March (Box 53)
        - Pamphlets
          - "Escuela Nueva" by Juan Manuel Echavarria, 1999 (Box 53)
          - "Menu" by Siobhan Gunning, Sean Laurenz, and Claire Clark, recipes by James Emanuel, 2000 (Box 53)
    - Issue 71, 2000 Spring
      - General (Box 38, 64)
      - Art
        - Moss, Stanley, 1987 February (Inscribed by the artist to Betsy Sussler) (Box 38, 64)
        - Rinn, Rivka, undated (Box 38, 64)
      - Art--Photographs--Museu de Serralves, Oporto, Portugal, undated (Box 38, 64)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 71)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 38)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 64)
      - Photographs--General (Box 64)
      - Portrait Photographs
        - After Life (Box 38)
        - Blade, Brian, undated (Box 38)
        - Blakely, Diann, 1999-2000 (Box 38)
        - Burton, Abraham, undated (Box 38)
        - Dangor, Achmat, 1999 (Box 38)
        - Douglas, Ellen, undated (Box 38)
        - Evans, Bill, undated (Box 38)
        - Evora, Cesaria, undated (Box 38)
        - Galaxy Craze, undated (Box 38)
        - Goldberg, Rose Lee, undated (Box 38)
        - Gray, Macy, undated (Box 38)
        - Guralnick, Peter, undated (Box 38)
        - Hahn, Kimiko, undated (Box 38)
        - Harvey, P.J., undated (Box 38)
        - Homes, A.M., 1999 (Box 38)
        - Lhasa, undated (Box 38)
        - Montero, Maya, 1999 May (Box 38)
        - Ondaatje, Michael, undated (Box 38)
        - Ribot, Marc, undated (Box 38)
        - Richard, Mark, 1998 (Box 38)
        - Said, Edward, undated (Box 38)
        - Soloff, Lew, 1999 (Box 38)
        - Toe 2000 Truckstop, undated (Box 38)
        - Winchester, Simon, 1998 (Box 38)
        - Unidentified Individuals (Box 38)
      - Printed Material--Pamphlets
        - "Androscoggin Too: The Pejepscot Poems" by Robert M. Chute (Inscribed by the author to Betsy Sussler), 1997 (Box 38)
        - "Elliot Schwartz: Selected Photographs," 1980-1996 (Box 38)
        - "Karen Gunderson: Night Garden Sunflowers," 1994 (Box 38)
        - "Jo Baer: Four Drawings," with a Commentary by Jo Baer and Bruce Robbins, 1993 (Box 38)
        - "Space Site Intervention: Situating Installation Art," undated (Box 38)
      - Printed Material--Playbill--Angels in America: Perestroika, Walter Kerr Theater, 1994 (Box 38)
      - Publicity Photographs
        - Americanos Latino Life in the United States, undated (Box 38)
        - Apt Pupil, 1998 (Box 38)
        - Ashes to Ashes," Roundabout Theatre Company, undated (Box 38)
        - Beloved, 1990 (Box 38)
        - The Celebration, 1998 (Box 38)
        - Central Station, 1998 (Box 38)
        - Cookie's Fortune, 1999 (Box 38)
        - Condo Painting, 2000 (Box 38)
        - De La Guardia, Daryl Roth Theatre (Box 38)
        - Elektra, undated (Box 38)
        - The Glass Menagerie, Yale Repertory Theater, 1999 (Box 38)
        - George Wallace, 1997 (Box 38)
        - The Iceman Cometh, Brooks Atkinson Theatre, undated (Box 38)
        - On the Ropes, 1999 (Box 38)
        - Potente, Franka, undated (Box 38)
        - Wanamaker, Zoe, undated (Box 38)
    - Issue 72, 2000 Summer
      - General (Box 64)
      - Audio Files (Box 113)
        - Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
        - Mini Disks (Box 113)
      - Digital Files (Box 71)
        - CD-R (Box 71)
        - Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 71)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 64)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 64)
      - Publicity Photographs (Box 64)
    - Issue 73, 2000 Fall
      - General (Box 1)
      - Audio Files (Box 113)
        - Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
        - Mini Disks (Box 113)
      - Digital Files (Box 71)
        - CD-R (Box 71)
        - Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 71)
      - Issue (Box 118)
    - Issue 74, 2000-2001 Winter
      - General (Box 104)
      - Audio Files (Box 113)
        - Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
        - Mini Disks (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 71)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 71, 104)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 104)
        - Choke by Chuck Palahniuk, 2000 (Box 104)
        - Investigating Sex: Surrealist Research, 1928-1932, edited by Jose Pierre, undated (Box 104)
        - Racism 101 by Nikki Giovanni, undated (Box 104)
      - Portrait Photographs--Goldman, Francisco, undated (Box 104)
    - Issue 75, 2001 Spring
      - General (Box 62)
      - Art--Photographs--Mead, George, 2000 (Box 62)
      - Audio Files (Box 113)
        - Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
        - Mini Disks (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 71)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks % (3 ½ inches) (Box 62)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Publicity Photographs--Kippur, 2000 (Box 62)
    - Issue 76, 2001 Summer
      - General (Box 6)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)